[
    {
        "title": "C:\\Users\\vedup\\PROJECT - Cross Lingual\\PROJECT\\Documents/en/Afghanistan_content.txt",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": " hippie trail",
                "question": "What was Afghanistan's essential stop on in the 1960's?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " Bamiyan",
                "question": "What is the name of the Buddha statues in Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " happy times",
                "question": "What were the Buddha statues of Bamiyan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " those days are gone",
                "question": "What did the Taliban destroy most of Afghanistan's monuments?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " peacekeeping troops",
                "question": "What type of troops are still operating in Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " travellers are advised against visiting Afghanistan",
                "question": "Why are travellers advised to travel to Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " increased bookings and interest",
                "question": "What has been reported in some quarters of a trip to Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " less than 20,000",
                "question": "How many tourists are there in Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " expensive",
                "question": "What are tours usually conducted in small groups?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " life has continued much the same as it has for centuries",
                "question": "How has life changed for many ordinary Afghans?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " surprising normality of Kabul",
                "question": "What does the few travellers that make it to Afghanistan tell of?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " melting pot of ethnic and tribal groups",
                "question": "What is Kabul a fascinating area of?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " tourism",
                "question": "What type of tourism could return to Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " personal security",
                "question": "What is recommended if you decide to travel to Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " 652,225 sq km",
                "question": "What is the area of Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " 33,369,945",
                "question": "What is the population of Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " 49.9 per sq km",
                "question": "What is the population density of Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " Kabul",
                "question": "What is the capital of Afghanistan?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " Emirate",
                "question": "What is Kabul's government?"
            },
            {
                "answer": " Mullah Mohammad Hassan Akhund",
                "question": "Who is the head of government in Kabul?"
            }
        ]
    }
]